The Real Charlie Chaplin is a documentary, drama film directed by James Spinney.
A look at the life and work of Charlie Chaplin in his own words featuring
an in-depth interview he gave to Life magazine in 1966.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Pearl Mackie.
Self (archive footage), played by Charlie Chaplin.
Charlie Chaplin 1966, played by Jeff Rawle.
Richard Meryman, played by Matthew Wolf.
Roddy McDowall, played by Dickie Beau.
Effie Wisdom, played by Anne Rosenfeld.
Charlie Chaplin is a 2002 Indian Tamil-language comedy film directed by Sakthi
Chidambaram, starring Prabhu and Prabhu Deva in the lead roles.
Abhirami, Gayathri Raguram and Livingston play other supporting roles.
It was released on 15 February 2002, and became a commercial success.
Prabhu won the Tamil Nadu State Film Award Special
Prize for his performance in the film.
The film's commercial success led to remakes in several languages, such as in Telugu as Pellam Oorelithe, Hindi as No Entry, Malayalam
as Happy Husbands, Kannada as Kalla Malla Sulla, Marathi as No Entry Pudhe Dhoka Aahey and in Bengali as Kelor Kirti.
The film explores themes of comedian, biography, actor.
The tone is emotional.